{
    "quizzes": [
        
        {
            "quizId": "0",
            "title": "Romance: Make a minestrone and we'll tell you who your Javascript method soulmate is",
            "author": "Firstname Lastname",
            
            "question1":{
                "question": "Choose an animal bone-based stock",
                "answers": ["Chicken stock", "Beef stock", "Water (aka fish stock)"]
            },
            "question2":{
                "question": "Choose additional vegetables beyond the core inclusion of onion, garlic, celery, tomatoes, and carrots",
                "answers": ["Zucchini", "Cabbage", "Kohlrabi"]
            },
            "question3":{
                "question": "Choose a carb-based addition",
                "answers": ["Rice", "Orzo pasta", "Diced potatoes"]
            },

            "url": "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1607528971899-2e89e6c0ec69?w=900&auto=format&fit=crop&q=60&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxzZWFyY2h8Nnx8c291cHxlbnwwfDB8MHx8fDA%3D"
        },
        {
            "quizId": "1",
            "title": "Personality: Pick your favorite number and we'll tell you what CSS selector you best embody",
            "author": "Firstname Lastname",

            "question1":{
                "question": "Pick a transcendental number",
                "answers": ["Ï€", "The paperfolding constant", "e^a if a is algebraic and non-zero, as proven by the Lindemann-Weierstrass theorem"]
            },
            "question2":{
                "question": "Select a large number",
                "answers": ["Rayo's number", "2^82589933, the largest known Mersenne prime", "Googol"]
            },
            "question3":{
                "question": "Choose an evil number",
                "answers": ["0","108","66"]
            },

            "url": "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1529078155058-5d716f45d604?q=80&w=2768&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D"
        },
        {
            "quizId": "2",
            "title": "Trivia:",
            "author": "Firstname Lastname",

            "question1":{
                "question": "Which method in the Document Object Model (DOM) can be used to make a new element?",
                "answers": ["document.createElement()",
                "document.newElement()",
                "document.addElement()",
                "document.create()"],
                "answer": "document.createElement()"
            },
            "question2":{
                "question": "How do you write a comment in JavaScript?",
                "answers": ["<!-- This is a comment -->",
                "// This is a comment",
                "'This is a comment",
                "/* This is a comment */"],
                "answer": "// This is a comment"
            },
            "question3":{
                "question": "In JavaScript, what is the result of trying to access an object property that does not exist?",
                "answers": ["null",
                "undefined",
                "0",
                "An error is thrown"],
                "answer": "undefined"
            },
            "question4":{
                "question": "Which attribute is used to specify that an input field must be filled out before submitting the form?",
                "answers": ["placeholder",
                "required",
                "validate",
                "necessary"],
                "answer": "required"
            },
            "question5":{
                "question": "How do you specify an alternative text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?",
                "answers": ["Using the 'alt' attribute in the <img> tag",
                "Using the 'description' attribute in the <img> tag",
                "Placing the text inside the <img> tag",
                "Using the 'src' attribute in the <img> tag"],
                "answer": "Using the 'alt' attribute in the <img> tag"
            },

            "url": "https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1621839673705-6617adf9e890?q=80&w=1932&auto=format&fit=crop&ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1wYWdlfHx8fGVufDB8fHx8fA%3D%3D"
        }

        
    ]
  }